day 30
I have a lot of ideas to put
I don't know a sawed-off toolbox
or some acrylic piece
do you know if you put my mark in the places
we can scale this business even further
and you can think of several things,
man
franchise model
expand
have my own brand you know
hello girls
all good
and now things are going brother
in a way
it's fast
is on
everything was going to be really cool
if i really wanted to continue
I happen to be Caio in the world man
my company is my profession
I am not a student
I'm just a guy trying to convey a message
and the message
she has to be always bigger than the messenger
is on
I proposed to set up a business
but with a greater purpose
what is fixing people's day
I've been on this road with a Passenger for 30 minutes
toolbox
and now I will invest in my company
hi man it's good
do you know where yasmin's house is
here on this street here
then you see Yasmin's house there
valeu valeu
and then it's fine
how are you
and you Jewel that I can take 1 of course
I'll take it with him
my god man
and hero people like you invisible
who's there in the fight
trapping in a place
fifty children
teaching without light that fixes people's days
it's really on
of people
then you do it is too big
and God is looking at you saw
here 1 little box for you in Brigadier
oh now is the time to return the horses bro
how come your face
too good
good too old
too much guy
the stop is as follows
he doesn't say a price to me no
ha ha you want to take him then
but you had talked about giving an entry and stuff
and what did you think about it bro
I don't have a lot of money now no bro
but I have R$1 old
this real valuable
good morning
then I get up quickly
tamo together hand
thank you old man it's us
if I become a businessman there too
how are you going to get part two of this all man
makes no sense